Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 2: Student Activities and Organizations, 1940-1997; 16 boxes; 1 folder
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps (R.O.T.C.), 1954-1976; 3 boxes
    - R.O.T.C. Evaluation and Consolidation, 1968-1976; 1 box
      - 1976 January-February, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - 1975, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - R.O.T.C. Promotional Materials, 1973; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - R.O.T.C. Information, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Report to the Council of the Princeton University Community, 1973 May-August; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Ad Hoc Committee Report to the Trustees, 1973 April-September; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Ad Hoc Committee Minutes and Notes, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Bicker Files, 1940-1997; 2 boxes
    - Bicker Clippings, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Bicker Reports, 1940-1963; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Bicker, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Bicker, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Bicker, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Bicker, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Bicker, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Bicker, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Master Copies of Sophomore Eligibility Lists, 1962; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Bicker, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Sophomore Eligible List, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Fall Bicker, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Bicker, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Fall Bicker, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Bicker, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Sophomore Eligible List, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Fall Bicker, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Bicker, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Bicker, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Fall Bicker, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Bicker, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Bicker, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Bicker, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Bicker, 1969; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Bicker Survey, 1970 February; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Eating Clubs, 1962-1989; 1 box
      - 1983-1984, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - 1975-1982, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - 1962-1974, 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Bicker, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Colonial Club, 1974-1982; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Terrace Club, 1969-1989; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Eating Clubs, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Clubs: Sophomore Choice Books, 1986-1997; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Eating Clubs, 1975-1990; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Lifestyle Colloquia, 1975-1989; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Student Orientation Guides, 1985-1994; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Outdoor Action, 1973-1993; 4 boxes
    - Frosh Trips Applications, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Frosh Trips Master File, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Leaders Frosh Trips, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Frosh Trips Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Frosh Trips Cancellations, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Frosh Trips Logistics, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Frosh Trips Food, Equipment and Transportation, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Frosh Trips Support, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Frosh Trips Money and Financial, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Frosh Trips Leader Packets, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Frosh Trips Waiting List, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Possible Leaders and Leader Lists, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Leaders, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Logistics, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Housing, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Frosh Trip Leader Applications, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Applications, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Equipment, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Food, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Suggestion/ Evaluation, ca., 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Money, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Infirmary, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Frosh Trips, 1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Frosh Trips Equipment, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Frosh Trips Correspondence, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Frosh Trips Food, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Frosh Trips Leader Packets, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Frosh Trips Leader Applications, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Leader Applications, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Frosh Trips Transportation, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Frosh Trips Cancellations, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Frosh Trips Regrets, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Frosh Trips Groups, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Frosh Trips Infirmary, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Frosh Trips RA/OA, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Frosh Trips, Housing, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Financial Aid, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Reimbursements, undated; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Trip Money, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Frosh Trips, Groups/Applications, 1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Frosh Trips, 1978; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Logistics, 1978; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Frosh Trips Participants and Cancellations, 1978; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Frosh Trips, Faculty and Staff, Third World Center, Food, 1978; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Frosh Trips, 1977; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Frosh Trips, 1977; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Frosh Trips Application Forms, 1977; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Pre-1977 Frosh Trips, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Frosh Trip, 1974; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Spring, 1975; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Frosh Trip, 1975; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Fall, 1975; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Spring, 1976; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Trip Applications, Spring, 1976; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Leader Evaluations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Fall, 1979; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Trip Applications, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Spring, 1979; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation, 1979; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Evaluation Forms, undated; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Spring, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Evaluations, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Frosh Trips, 1977; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Evaluations, 1978; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Old Evaluation Letters, undated; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Evaluation Letters, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Program Suggestions, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Leader Training Evaluations, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Routes/Trip Logs, 1979; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Incomplete Orders, 1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Sources, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Equipment Purchases, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Equipment Purchases, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Equipment Purchases, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Liberty Organization Inc, 1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Trip Applications, Spring, 1978; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Spring, 1978; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Fall, 1978; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Evaluations, 1979; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Credit Card Accounts, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Peruvian Mountain Climbing, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Outdoor Action - Kayaking, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Finance Statements, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Outdoor Action, 014-0064, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Outdoor Action, 645-1025, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Outdoor Action, 645-2006, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Old Outdoor Action Finance Files, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Old Outdoor Action Finance Files, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Old Outdoor Action Finance Files, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Magazine Subscriptions, 1979; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Meetings, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Billing for Vehicle Use, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Participant Evaluations, Freshman Trips, 1993; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Freshman Trips 1993 General, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 47, Folder 15-16)
    - Freshman Trips 1992, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Freshman Trips 1990, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Series 3: Committees, 1912-1993; 10 boxes
  The Committees series contains records documenting the Dean of Students' participation on university committees. Most of the committees, such as the Dormitory Development Committee and the Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life, relate directly to the Office's responsibilities in their mission. The records consist largely of correspondence, memoranda, and meeting minutes.
  Arranged by committee.
  - Ivy Group Committee, 1912-1968; 1 box
    - Arbor Inn, 1925-1938; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Club Plan - Mathey Memorandum, 1935; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Histories - Clubs, 1928-1964; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Car Rule, 1967; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Court Club, 1952-1964; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Discipline Cases, 1912-1948; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Gateway Club, 1936-1941; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Steven Rockefeller, "Reflections on the Princeton Club System and the 1958 Bicker," 1960, 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Library for New University Club, 1937; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Ivy Group Committee on Coordination and Eligibility, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Ivy Group Committee on Coordination and Eligibility, Minutes, 1939-1964; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association - Ivy, Key Documents, 1966-1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Ivy - National Collegiate Athletics Association - Publicity, 1966; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Madison Club, 1932-1937; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Off-Campus Living, Spring, 1968; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Parking Requirements, 1967; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Prospect Club, 1950-1960; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Dean of the College: Miscellaneous - Conditions of Undergraduate Life, 1929-1954; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Dormitory Development Committee, 1956-1967; 1 box
    - Dormitory Development Committee, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Joint Faculty - Administrative Dormitory Development Committee, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Dormitory Clippings, 1956-1958; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Dormitory Development - Minutes, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Dormitory Development - Joint Committee, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Enrollment, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Enrolment and Dormitory Occupancy, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Committee- Athletic Eligibility, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Mayor's Committee, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators, 1968; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Civil Defense Committee - Fall-Out Protection, 1961-1965; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Parietals, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Student Activism - Rights, Representation, Etc, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Student Records Committee and Related, 1966 December; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1967 September; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1968 June; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Drug Use, Etc. - Magrath/Lippincott Correspondence, 1967; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Columbia, 1968; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Committee on the Handicapped, 1977-1983; 1 box
    - Advisory Committee on the Handicapped, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Self-Evaluation Report on the Policies Regarding Handicapped Individuals, 1978 July; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Handicapped, 1979; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Handicapped at Princeton, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous - Handicapped, 1978; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Transition Plan for Building Accessibility, 1978-1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Computer Information, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Glossary of Federal Terms, 1977; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Athletics and Physical Education, 1981-1993; 1 box
    - Athletics Letters, 1981-1988; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - History of Physical Education, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Physical Education Requirement, 1987-1990; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Athletics, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Athletics, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Athletics/Physical Education, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life, 1971-1990; 3 boxes
    - Student Organizations, 1978 March; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Memos - Building Services and Housing, 1978 March-April; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Student Life Committee - Correspondence, Statistics, 1975; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - March 13 Session, 1978 February 22; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Social and Dining Options Committee, 1978; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Agenda, 1978 April 20; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Interim Report of the Subcommittee on Food Services, 1978 May 2; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Subcommittee Report on Cultural and Athletic Affairs, 1978 May 19; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Progress Report, 1978 May 19; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Subcommittee on Social Facilities - Preliminary Report, 1978 May 19; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Report on Residential Life, 1975; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Richard E. Spies, 1978 July 27; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Progress Report, 1978 July; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Agenda, 1978 July 19; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Modeling, 1978 August-September; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Jon D. Hlafter, Social/Dining Models, 1978; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Committee Meetings, 1978 September-October; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - University/Clubs Relationship, Fall, 1978; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Interim Report, 1978 December 1; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Second Interim Report, 1978 December 27; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Meetings with Eating Clubs, 1979; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Report, 1979 April 10; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Report for Trustees Subcommittee on Residential Life, 1978 March 29; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - ABPA Executive Committee Statement, 1979 April 12; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Distribution of Upperclassmen into Prospect Street Facilities, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Ad Hoc Group - Neil L. Rudenstine, 1980 April 15; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Press Releases, Memo Reports, Miscellaneous, Etc, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Reports and Response, Correspondence, Etc, 1979; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Princeton University Club Study, 1975 March; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Report, 1979; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Interim Reports, 1978 July-December; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Planning Meetings, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Planning Meetings, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Report - Final Draft, 1978; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Committee for Social and Dining Options, 1978; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Kitchen Surveys, Distribution of Undergraduate Board Contracts, 1973; 1978; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Progress Report, 1978; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Report and Supplement, Miscellaneous, 1971-1979; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous - Subcommittee on Cultural and Athletic Affairs, Dormitory Overcrowding, Etc, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Memo - Report, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Appendix Part II, 1979; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Report on Policy Issues related to Commons, Sophomore Dining Contracts and the Prospect Street Clubs, 1971; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Assorted Memos, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Public Interest Research Groups Issue, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Pornographic Films Issue, 1981; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Old Material, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 1983-1984, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Report on Residential Life, 1975; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Report on the Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life, 1979; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Princeton Dormitory Study, 1977 September; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Princeton Weekly Bulletin - Upperclass Residential Life, 1981 September 28; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Interim Reports, 1978 July-December; 2 folders (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
  - Latino Advisory Committee, 1985-1992; 1 box
    - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Hispanic Issues, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Latino Lecture Series Committee, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Latino Lectures, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Heritage of Faith Colloquium, 1988; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Latino Students, 1986; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Minority Affairs Committee, 1967-1993; 1 box
    - Minority Students - Archival, 1967-1982; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - 1991-1992, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - 1992-1993, 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Council of Masters of Residential Colleges, 1982 August-1990; 1 box
    - 1982 August-October, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1982 November-1983 January, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 1983 January-February, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 1983 March-June, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 1983 September-October, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 1983 November-1984 June, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 1984 September-December, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - 1985 January-June, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - 1987 September-December, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - 1988 January-May, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - International Center, 1984-1993; 1 box
    - 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - 1990-1991, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - 1991-1992, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - 1992-1993, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Women's Center, 1981-1993; 1 box
    - 1981-1982, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - 1982-1983, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - 1983-1984, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - 1990-1991, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - 1991-1992, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - 1992-1993, 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Inter-Club Committee, 1947-1953; 1 box
    - Minutes, 1947-1952; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Bicker and Elections, 1953; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, Press Clippings, Etc, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, Press Clippings, Etc, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, Press Clippings, Etc, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, Press Clippings, Etc, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Princeton Broadcasting Services Incorporated - Annual Report of the Station Manager, 1952 November 1; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators: 36th Anniversary Conference - Proceedings, 1954 May 1-4, 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - The Honor System - Acknowledgement of Sources - Undergraduate Regulations, 1967 June 30; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Committees, 1960-1977; 1 box
    - Trustees' Curriculum Committee, 1970 March 1; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 1)
      [restricted until 2020]
    - Trustees' Committee on Student Life, 1973 September 28; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 2)
      [restricted until 2023]
    - Trustees' Committee on Student Life, 1960-1977; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 3)
      [restricted until 2027]
    - Trustees' Committee on Student Life, S. B. Penick, Jr, 1968; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 4)
      [restricted until 2018]
    - Bressler Commission, 1973; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Committee on Undergraduate Life, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Committee on Undergraduate Life, 1971; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Committee on Undergraduate Life, 1960-1970; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Honor Committee, 1971; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Trustees' Special Committee on Clubs, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Trustees' Special Committee on Clubs, 1968 January-June; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Trustees' Committee on Student Life, Health, and Athletics, 1971; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 12)
      [restricted until 2021]
    - Trustees' Committee on Student Life, Health, and Athletics, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 13)